Please do not attempt to perform
any of these stunts
Or activities in this show.
They are super dangerous,
crazy, wild, dangerous.
The stunts seen are either
performed by professionals
Or under the supervision
of professionals,
Serious professionals.
This show also
contains bad language.
♪
Case:
Legendary portland spot.
Few people have tried it.
It's never been done.
Jaws is about to conquer.
That shit's fucked.
Hey, fuck it.
I'm gonna do it.
Man:
You have first try, dude.
Give me the connection,
like this.
Like this.
No, no, no.
Fingers in the middle.
You have to do it.
You're on the session.
All right, let's go.
All right. Later!
-You got this, dawg!
-Fuckin' do it!
♪ just to slow down
Homoki: Fuck!
-All right.
Right here. Right here.
Man: Yes, dude.
You got that, easy.
Man: Hold up, hold up.
You got it?
♪ just to slow down
♪ I have precision
-Yeah!
-[ laughs ]
Homoki: All right,
let's fuckin' do this.
Let's fuckin' do this!
Whoo!
♪
[ cheers and applause ]
Man: Yeah!
♪ raw oysters, texas pete
♪ sea urchin on the reef
♪ sour cheeseburger
man: Oh!
♪ bit to eat
♪ lick butter goes with keef
man: Oh!
♪ into the cocoa leaf
♪ fresh maggots on my teeth
aah!
Aah!
♪ they're cheap
♪ oh, baby
♪
Whoo!
Ouch.
♪
We got 31 days clean and sober
in a day.
Right now,
I'm like one city ahead of them.